<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tour Guide</string>

    <string name="historical">Historical</string>
    <string name="museums">Museums</string>
    <string name="food">Food</string>
    <string name="other">Other</string>

    <string name="aga_khan_palace">Aga Khan Palace</string>
    <string name="aga_khan_palace_description">The Aga Khan Palace in Pune occupies a prime
        position in the history of India’s freedom movement for the fact that Mahatma Gandhi,
        his wife, secretary and others were incarcerated here from 1942. It now serves as the
        headquarters of the Gandhi National Memorial Society where the making of ‘khadi’ continues
        to be a prime activity. This imposing palace where one can feel an intense connection with
        the past is also known for its beautiful and serene gardens.</string>

    <string name="shaniwar_wada">Shaniwar Wada</string>
    <string name="shaniwar_wada_description">Shaniwarwada was the stately mansion originally built
        as the residence of the Peshwas. The foundation of the mansion was laid by Bajirao 1 in the
        year 1730 AD and construction was completed in 1732 AD at a cost of Rs. 16,120. Several
        additions were made to the palace like fortification walls with bastions, gates and court
        halls by his successors.</string>

    <string name="sinhagad_fort">Sinhagad Fort</string>
    <string name="sinhagad_fort_description">As one of the top military outposts during the reign
        of Chhatrapati Shivaji Maharaj, the fort of Sinhagad not only offers a fascinating peek
        into the history of the Maratha Empire but is also a perennial favourite with trekkers
        and the residents of Pune because of its proximity to the city. While standing atop the
        hill and taking in the panoramic view of the landscape below, you cannot help but wonder
        at the vision of those who built such imposing structures at such great heights</string>

    <string name="national_war_museum">National War Museum</string>
    <string name="national_war_museum_description">The National War Museum is a result of public’s
        initiative to set up some museums in fond memory of the Indian soldiers who laid down
        their lives for the nation. The citizens of Pune, under the Express Citizens’
        Forum established the War Memorial Fund. Thus funds were collected from the citizens of
        the country for this noble cause. From the rich business executives to the common man,
        all contributed to this fund according to their abilities. Then the foundation of the
        National War Museum was laid in November 1977 and finally opened for the public in
        October 1998.</string>

    <string name="raja_dinkar_kelkar_museum">Raja Dinkar Kelkar Museum</string>
    <string name="raja_dinkar_kelkar_museum_description">Kelkar Museum was established in 1962 by
        Baba Dinkar Kelkar and was donated to the Maharashtra government in 1975. The museum
        has 20,000 different articles, all personally collected by Baba Kelkar from all over
        the world. When his son died at the age of seven, he decided to do something in his
        remembrance and that is how the idea of building this museum was conceived.</string>

    <string name="darshan_museum">Darshan Museum</string>
    <string name="darshan_museum_description">The Darshan museum is a biographical museum that is
        dedicated to the Life and teaching of Sadhu Vaswani, the modern Sindhi spiritual leader.
        A visit to this museum can be a transforming experience in many ways. The museum is built
        on the first floor of the Sadhu Vaswani mission building. It covers a huge area of
        10000 sq. ft and hordes of visitors are charmed by this place daily. It is designed to
        engage people in a modernistic, rich in multimedia way with a number of interactive
        exhibits.</string>

    <string name="joshi_museum">Joshi\'s Museum of Miniature Railways</string>
    <string name="joshi_museum_description">Joshi\'s Museum of Miniature Railway is a miniature
        railway museum located in the Karve Road locality of Pune, a city in the state of
        Maharashtra, India. The museum hosts working models of various types of trains.
        It was started by Bhausaheb Joshi.</string>

    <string name="vaishali">Vaishali</string>
    <string name="vaishali_description">Vaishali is one of the most popular restaurant among the
        student community of Pune, Situated on the Fergusson College Road. Vaishali attracts all
        the college crowd. The ambience is youthful and price factor is also average and that is
        the main reason why Vaishali has become a hot hang out of Pune’s student community.</string>

    <string name="cafe_goodluck">Cafe Goodluck</string>
    <string name="cafe_goodluck_description">Good Luck Cafe is a popular Irani cafe-restaurant
        on the Fergusson College Road, in the Deccan Gymkhana area of Pune, India. Established
        in 1935 by Hussain Ali Yakshi, it is one of the oldest Irani places in Pune. Good luck cafe
        is most famous for it bun maska/bun omelette and Iranian tea among the other dishes.
        The place is always crowded and especially popular among the youngsters.</string>

    <string name="jj_garden">JJ Garden Wada Pav</string>
    <string name="jj_garden_description">Vada pav at the Garden Vada Pav Centre is truly exceptional
        and Garden Wada Pav is a name which most pune wala\'s are familiar with. The place has
        been serving what many claim is the “best wada pav” in town for over three generations.
        It is evident by the crowd which is present any time of the day. Though a roadside shop,
        it is famous for its taste and their Chutney is the differentiator.</string>

    <string name="kalyan_bhel">Kalyan Bhel House</string>
    <string name="kalyan_bhel_description">Kalyan Bhel House is a renowned chaat and snack house
        operating since the last 30 years in Pune. The goal is to satisfy the hunger of chaat and
        snack lover’s and having loyal customers all year around. Kalyan Bhel House is famous,
        popular and unique because of is its delicious and yummy food, walking distance locations,
        scintillating ambience, cleanliness and hygiene, and above all friendly staff.</string>

    <string name="dagduseth_temple">Dagduseth Temple</string>
    <string name="dagduseth_temple_description">Srimanth Dagaduseth Ganpati temple pune is one of
        the most important and visited ganesh temple in Maharashtra. Dagaduseth seth ganpati temple
        is visited by millions of people on ganesh chaturthi and the ten day festival celebration
        of Ganesh chaturthi.The Lord Ganesh temple is situated at a walking distance from the
        famous historical monument called Shaniwar Wada, which used to be the administrative
        headquarter during the Peshwa Regime.</string>

    <string name="parvati">Parvati</string>
    <string name="parvati_description">Parvati is one of the favourite relaxation spots for the
        residents of Pune. The height of Parvati hill is 2100 feet above sea level and 260 feet
        from the city level. The hill offers an aerial view of the city and the most picturesque
        scene in the early hours of the day. Parvati hill houses one big and three small 
        temples.</string>

    <string name="nda">National Defence Academy</string>
    <string name="nda_description">The National Defence Academy (NDA) is the Joint Services academy 
        of the Indian Armed Forces, where cadets of the three services, the Army, the Navy and 
        the Air Force train together before they go on to pre-commissioning training in their
        respective service academies. The NDA is located at Khadakwasla near Pune, Maharashtra. 
        It is the first tri-service academy in the world.</string>

    <string name="khadakwasla">Khadakwasla Dam</string>
    <string name="khadakwasla_description">Khadakwasla Dam is a dam on the Mutha River 20 km (12 mi)
        from the city of Pune in Maharashtra, India. This dam across the river Mutha created an
        attractive lake, now known as Khadakwasla Lake. This lake is the main source of water for
        Pune and its suburbs.</string>
</resources>
